So the first one,
لذا أول شيء،
the typo in David.
الخطأ المطبعي في كلمة David.
D_s_v_i_d versus D_a_v_i_d, and it's displayed here.
D_s_v_i_d مقابل D_a_v_i_d، وتعرض هنا.
This is an accuracy issue.
هذه مشكلة الدقة.
There's nothing illegal about having the name D_s_v_i_d,
لا يوجد شيء غير قانوني بشأن وجود اسم D_s_v_i_d،
so it's not invalid, it's just inaccurate.
هذا ليس غير صالح، ولكنه فقط غير دقيق.
And the next one.
والنقطة التالية.
The letter U in the dosage information for Auralin and Novodra.
حرف U في معلومات عن الجرعة لكل من Auralin وNovodra.
Once again, this is just the fact that the U is present.
مرة أخرى، الحقيقة هي وجود U.
This is a validity issue.
هذه مشكلة التحقق.
23u is not a valid dose.
23u ليست الجرعة الصالحة.
The valid dose is 23,
ولكن الجرعة الصالحة هي 23.
and the unit of measurement is U,
ووحدة القياس هي U،
or units, insulin units.
أو وحدات أو وحدات أنسولين.
We can't perform calculations with 23u.
لا يمكننا إجراء الحسابات مع 23u.
This goes hand-in-hand with the wrong data type validity issue.
يسير هذه جنبًا إلى جنب مع مشكلة التحقق من نوع البيانات الخاطئة.
But we'll physically have to remove the U,
ولكن سيجب علينا فعليًا إزالة حرف U،
instead of just changing the data type.
بدلًا من تغيير نوع البيانات.
Pandas won't accept something with the letter U in it as an integer or float.
لن تقبل Pandas شيئًا يوجد به حرف U كعدد صحيح أو عدد عشري.
It will force it to the data type object,
ستدفعها إلى كائن نوع البيانات،
which is how strings are represented in Pandas.
وهو عبارة عن كيفية تمثيل السلاسل في Pandas.
So again, this is invalid.
مرة أخرى، هذا أمر غير صالح.
23u is right, it's just the wrong representation.
23u صحيحة، ولكنه الأمر مجرد تمثيل خاطئ.
It's not according to the defined schema of this table.
إنه ليس وفقًا للمخطط المحدد لهذا الجدول.
The next one, the lowercase given names and
النقطة التالية، استخدام الأحرف الصغيرة لأسماء محددة
surnames and treatments and adverse reactions.
وألقاب وعلاجات وردود الفعل العكسية.
Treatments, adverse reactions.
العلاجات وردود الفعل العكسية.
Let's zoom out a bit here.
لنلق نظرة شاملة هنا.
So I'd argue that this is a consistency issue.
إذًا، سأرجح إن هذه مشكلة التناسق.
It's not necessarily a big deal that the given names and surnames are in lowercase.
كتابة الأسماء المحددة والألقاب بالأحرف الصغيرة ليس بالضرورة أمرًا كبيرًا.
So that removes the inaccurate part.
حتى يزيل الجزء غير الدقيق.
It's just that in the patients table,
في جدول المرضى فقط،
the names are capitalized.
الأسماء مكتوبة بأحرف كبيرة.
So you'd run into issues when joining these tables based on name.
لذا ستواجهكم مشكلة عند دمج هذه الجداول بناءً على الاسم.
This is an inconsistent representation of name across tables in this dataset.
هذا تمثيل غير متناسق للاسم في الجداول في مجموعة البيانات.
Pandas in Python doesn't recognize
لن تتعرف Pandas في Python
lowercase strings as the exact same as capitalized strings.
على سلاسل الأحرف الصغيرة على أنها نفس سلاسل الأحرف الكبيرة.
So that's where the issue stems from.
وهنا تكمن المشكلة.
And the final one: missing records in the treatments table,
والنقطة الأخيرة: السجلات المفقودة في جدول العلاجات،
280 instead of 350.
280 بدلًا من 350.
This is pretty straightforward,
هذا واضح للغاية.
this is a completeness issue.
هذه مشكلة الإنجاز.
We don't have all the records that we need.
ليس لدينا كل السجلات التي نحتاجها.